<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>devops - Tag - Knowledge Base</title>
        <link>https://jolly-field-0e8c05903.2.azurestaticapps.net/tags/devops/</link>
        <description>devops - Tag - Knowledge Base</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>blog@duijzer.com (Jacob Duijzer)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>blog@duijzer.com (Jacob Duijzer)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 13:43:35 &#43;0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jolly-field-0e8c05903.2.azurestaticapps.net/tags/devops/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Team Topologies</title>
    <link>https://jolly-field-0e8c05903.2.azurestaticapps.net/team-topologies/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 13:43:35 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Jacob Duijzer</author>
    <guid>https://jolly-field-0e8c05903.2.azurestaticapps.net/team-topologies/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Team Topologies: is an excellent guide to structuring and keeping teams, processes and technologies aligned, for all kinds of organisations. It gives us a vocabulary and a model to direct our thinking in a way that allows for scaling up, and helps us to organise teams for effective software development.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Accelerate: Building and Scaling High Performing Technology Organizations</title>
    <link>https://jolly-field-0e8c05903.2.azurestaticapps.net/accelerate/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 16:29:07 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Jacob Duijzer</author>
    <guid>https://jolly-field-0e8c05903.2.azurestaticapps.net/accelerate/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>How can we apply technology to drive business value? For years, we’ve been told that the performance of software delivery teams doesn’t matter―that it can’t provide a competitive advantage to our companies. Through four years of groundbreaking research to include data collected from the State of DevOps reports conducted with Puppet, Dr. Nicole Forsgren, Jez Humble, and Gene Kim set out to find a way to measure software delivery performance―and what drives it―using rigorous statistical methods. This book presents both the findings and the science behind that research, making the information accessible for readers to apply in their own organizations.</p>]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
